<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!-- Global string to be used in app -->

<resources>
	<string name="app_name">Domotica</string>
	<string name="openDrawer">Drawer Open</string>
	<string name="closeDrawer">Drawer Closed</string>
	<string name="Home">Home</string>
	<string name="Switches1">Switches</string>
	<string name="Sensors1">Sensors</string>
	<string name="Sensors2">Sensors</string>
	<string name="Switches2">Timers</string>
	<string name="Connection">Connection</string>
	<string name="Mode">Modes</string>
	<string name="FAQ">FAQ</string>
	<string name="sensorName1">Temperature Sensor</string>
	<string name="sensorName2">Light Sensor</string>
	<string name="listShortClick">Hold Items to see options</string>
	<string-array name="SensorNames">
		<item>Temperature Sensor</item>
		<item>Light Sensor</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="Relations">
		<item>Lower Than</item>
		<item>Greater Than</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="Switches">
		<item>Switch 1</item>
		<item>Switch 2</item>
		<item>Switch 3</item>
		<item>Switch 4</item>
		<item>All Switches</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="Mode">
		<item>Switch Mode</item>
		<item>Threshold Mode</item>
		<item>Timer Mode</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="Bools">
		<item>On</item>
		<item>Off</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="HomeText">
		<font size='16'> <b>Welcome to our home automation application. Click on the top left menu icon to open the menu or swipe to the right to open it.</b></font>\n
		\n<font size='14'>With this awesome app you are able to control (almost) everything in your house. For example ; your light, TV, coffee maker etc.\n
		\nWith this app you are able to control sockets by means of switches which can be controlled by this app.\n<b>Make sure to make connection first before using the app!</b>\nFor connection instructions go to the FAQ in the menu.\n\nYou can read the sensorvalues (temperature and light) and set threshholds which are connected to the switches.\nThreshholds are used to control your switches that are affected by sensorvalues.\ne.g: Set sensorValue threshhold on &lt; (lower) than 200 on switch 2, this means switch 2 will react when the sensorvalue gets lower than 200.\nThese instructions are also written in the FAQ.\n
		</font>
	</string>
	<string name="SwitchHelp">
		With this page you can control the sockets with the switches.\n
		\nPlease be sure to connect to the Arduino and select the \"Switch Mode\" on the modes page.
		\nTo sync the states of the switches with the states of the sockets press the \"Refresh Switches\" button.
	</string>
	<string name="SensorsHelp">
		With this page you can read the values of the sensors and set thresholds for the sensor values.\n
		\n<b>Reading Sensor values</b>\n
		\nMake Sure you\'re in \"Threshold Mode\".
		\nPress Refresh Sensors to refresh the sensor values once.
		\nPress Toggle Refresh to toggle the sensor refresh on a timer.\n
		\n<b>Set Thresholds</b>\n
		\nPress the plus sign in the top right next to the questionmark.
		\n- Select Sensor
		\n- Choose if value should be higher or lower
		\n- Enter value
		\n- Choose what switch should be toggled if condition is true\n
		\nNote: Thresholds only work if \"Threshold Mode\" is selected and Toggle Refresh is on.
	</string>
	<string name="TimersHelp">
		With this page you can set a time on with a switch should be toggled.
		\nFor this feature to work make sure \"Timer Mode\" is selected.\n
		\n<b>To add a Time</b>\n
		\nPress the plus sign in the top right next to the questionmark.
		\n- Enter a time(24h clock)
		\n- Select what switch should be toggled
		\n- Select to what state the switch should toggle
		\n
	</string>
	<string name="ConnectionHelp">
		With this page you can establish a connecion with the arduino.
		\nEnter the ip (default is 192.168.4.10) and the port number(default is 32545).
		\nThe message on the page will change accoardingly to a failed or succesful connection.\n
		\nNote: You need a connection with the aruino to be able to use features in this app.
		\n
	</string>
	<string name="ModesHelp">
		With this page you can choose an mode. The mode indicates what features of the app are active.\n
		\n<b>Modes</b>
		\n- Switch Mode: Use switches to toggle the sockets manualy.
		\n- Thershold Mode: Set thresholds for sensor values.
		\n- Timer Mode: Set a time on with the socket should be toggled.
		\n
	</string>
</resources>
